# Mariano Ignacio Bonfanti

TALLERS 47 PISO 2, BARCELONA, ESPAÑA 08001 +34 671221655

**BONFANTIMARIANO@GMAIL.COM** 

HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/BONFANTIMARIANO/



#### **PROFILE**

Professional specialised in the area of software engineering oriented to the creation of digital services and products. Currently taking my first steps as a full stack developer in a start up. My main strengths are willingness to face challenging projects, strong analytical skills and constant creativity applied to solve problems and achieve goals. Also excellent interpersonal skills and very adaptable to multicultural teams.

## **EXPERIENCE**

DEVELOPER, HECTOR KITCHEN; BARCELONA, ESPAÑA - 2018-PRESENT

Develop and perform scalable maintenance on web, micro-services and mobile app based primarily on C#, HTML5, MySQL, AngularJs, Cordova, NodeJS and Python.

DEVELOPER, FOLDER IT; SANTA FE, SANTA FE - 2017-2018

Development of responsive web applications. Angular 4 / Spring framework / PostgreSQL

INDEPENDENT DEVELOPER; SANTA FE, SANTA FE - 2016-2017

Development of custom mobile applications with the following technologies: HTML, JavaScript, jQuery Mobile, Ionic+AngularJS, Apache Cordova.

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING, ACCENTURE; ROSARIO, SANTA FE - 2011-2015

SAP BI - Project AES - Management of InforProviders, multiproviders, infoCubes and maintenance of the DataWarehouse model.

SAP FI - Project YPF - Mainly in charge of requirements analysis and configurations in the Finance module. In some cases, specific modifications in ABAP code (SAP Programming language).

TECHNICAL ASSISTANT, UNIVERSIDAD ABIERTA INTERAMERICANA; ROSARIO, ARGENTINA – 2012-2014

In charge of the university computer labs. Technical assistance to students and teachers.

#### **EDUCATION**

Universidad abierta interamericana, Rosario, Argentina - Information System Engineer – 2008-2013

### **SKILLS**

.NET - C# - JavaScript - MySQL - AngularJs - NodeJs - Cordova - iOs, Swift - PHP - Java - Phyton PostgresSQL - MongoDB - ABAP - Git/GitHub - Docker - Atlassian tools - Octupus.

#### **REFERENCES**

Luciano Molinas - Manager in Accenture - luciano.molinas@accenture.com Daniel Tedini - Vice Dean UAI - daniel.tedini@uai.edu.ar Facundo Farias - CTO at Happets - facundo.farias@gmail.com